{
  "Fact":
  [
    {"Question" : "A prostitute in 18th-century France could avoid punishment by", "Answer" : "Joining the opera"},
    {"Question" : "According to the Scottish Protection of Animals Act of 1912, this is a protected species", "Answer" : "The Loch Ness Monster"},
    {"Question" : "Ancient Romans paid their taxes with", "Answer" : "Honey"},
    {"Question" : "World second highest mountain is", "Answer" : "K2"},
    {"Question" : "Cloacina was the Roman goddess of", "Answer" : "Sewers"},
    {"Question" : "Beethoven did this every time he made a cup of coffee", "Answer" : "Counted out exactly 60 beans"},
    {"Question" : "Ernest Hemingway once wrote a six-word short story that reads", "Answer" : "For Sale: Baby Shoes, Never Worn"},
    {"Question" : "During the first Crusade, English knights spent their entire campaign fund on", "Answer" : "Prostitutes"},
    {"Question" : "During hot weather, the Eiffel Tower", "Answer" : "Grows around 6 inches"},
    {"Question" : "Edward Elgar is the only major composer who mastered", "Answer" : "The Bassoon"},
    {"Question" : "Hans Christian Anderson was terrified of", "Answer" : "Naked women"},
    {"Question" : "Humphrey Bogart’s last words were", "Answer" : "I should never have switched from scotch to martinis"},
    {"Question" : "Found in Mesopotamia, the world’s first written recipe was for", "Answer" : "Beer"},
    {"Question" : "In 1535, Henry VIII put a tax on", "Answer" : "Beards"},
    {"Question" : "The ancient Chinese believed that the thicker your earlobe,", "Answer" : "The more wealth you have"},
    {"Question" : "The ancient Greeks used to do this to the inside of wine glasses", "Answer" : "Paint obscene pictures"},
    {"Question" : "The Aztecs of Mexico wore this food item as jewelry", "Answer" : "Popcorn"},
    {"Question" : "The inventor of the trampoline showed off his creation by jumping on it with", "Answer" : "Kangaroo"},
    {"Question" : "The inventors of bubble wrap were trying to make", "Answer" : "Easy-wipe textured wallpaper"},
    {"Question" : "The National Anthem of Bangladesh includes the line: The fragrance from your mango groves…", "Answer" : "Makes me wild with joy"},
    {"Question" : "The number 88 is Morse code shorthand for", "Answer" : "Love and kisses"},
    {"Question" : "The only female pharaoh of Egypt wore", "Answer" : "A fake beard"},
    {"Question" : "The soil on Mars is good for growing", "Answer" : "Asparagus"},
    {"Question" : "The work originated in the Bronze Age and was used by Mongolians as", "Answer" : "A helmet that doubled as a cooking pan"},
    {"Question" : "This book has inspired more pop songs than any other", "Answer" : "The King James Bible"},
    {"Question" : "When in need for inspiration, Ludwig van Beethoven would", "Answer" : "Pour water on himself"},
    {"Question" : "When giving speeches, Sarkozy made himself look taller by", "Answer" : "Hiring short people to stand behind him"},
    {"Question" : "When George Washington campaigned in Virginia in 1758, he bough this for every eligible voter", "Answer" : "Three pints of alcohol"},
    {"Question" : "When a cat died in ancient Egypt, its owners did this as a sign of mourning", "Answer" : "Shaved their eyebrows"},
    {"Question" : "Walt Disney intended for the EPCOT center to serve as", "Answer" : "An experimental model utopian society"},
    {"Question" : "Visitors to Alcatraz report hearing this from inside Al Capone’s old jail cell", "Answer" : "Banjo music"},
    {"Question" : "Typewriters used to be known as", "Answer" : "Literary pianos"},
    {"Question" : "Tobacco companies use cat litter to", "Answer" : "Make their cigars bigger"},
    {"Question" : "William A. Calderwood patented furniture that was", "Answer" : "Filled with helium so that it could float to the ceiling when not in use"},
    {"Question" : "Wrigley’s was originally a producer of this product", "Answer" : "Soap"}
  ]
}